allseated.com 2017-09-25

# Privacy Policy - AllSeated: Seating charts, floor plans, and guest lists for your event

**AllSeated Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated: 5/15/17**

Protecting your privacy is really important to us. With this in mind, we’re providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive through our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use (“ **TOU** ”). So, please make sure that you have read and understand our TOU.

## **Revisions to this Privacy Policy**

Any information that is collected via our Services is covered by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll update the “Last Updated Date” above to indicate when those changes will become effective.

## **Collection and Use of Information**

**Information Collected or Received from You**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are a Host, Venue, Vendor or User), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services.

_Account Information_. If you create an Account, we may collect certain information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, email address, postal address and phone number (“ **PII** ”) directly from you or from other Account holders in connection with an Event, as indicated in the TOU. We may also collect your gender, date of birth and other information that is not considered PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you.

_Information Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies_. Like many website owners and operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to collect certain information.

“ **Cookies** ” are small text files that are placed on your device by a web server when you access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own Cookies on your hard drive. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties.

“ **Web Beacons** ” (also known as web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes, including to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, to monitor how many visitors view our Services, and to monitor the effectiveness of our advertising. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the device, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly on web pages (or in an e-mail).

_Information Related to Use of the Services_. Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “ **Log Data** ”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “ **Visitor** ”). Log Data may include information such as a Visitor’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a Visitor was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a Visitor browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a Visitor clicked on and other statistics. We use Log Data to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve, customize and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Visitors’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used.

_Information Sent by Your Device_. We collect certain information that your device sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings and the operating system of your device, as well as information about your use of our Services.

_Location Information_. When you use our Services, we may collect and store information about your location by converting your IP address into a rough geo-location or by accessing your mobile device’s GPS coordinates or coarse location if you enable location services on your device. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. If you do not want us to collect location information from your mobile device, you may disable that feature on your mobile device.

### **Information that We Share with Third Parties**

We will not share any PII that we have collected from or regarding you except as described below:

_Information Shared with Other Account Holders_. As a collaborative event planning platform, Event information is shared between Account holders (i.e., registered Users) and other Users who are invited to the same Event. For example, as a Host, if you invite another User to your Event page on the Services, that User will see the Event specific information you have provided to describe your Event, including the event date, number of guests, venue, furniture layout and guest list. With respect to floorplan information you provide to the Services, if you specify that the floorplan is a private residence the label or title you give the floorplan will only be known to you and those that you invite to your Event page.  Also, if you join an Event, any Host, Vendor or other User associated with that Event will be able to see that you are connected to that Event. The information you provide about your Event is voluntary. We recommend that you guard your sensitive information and we encourage Users to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose on their Event pages.

In addition, as a Host, you may choose to contact a Vendor through the Services using our Vendor Matching feature. If you click on a “Contact Vendor” link within the Services, the applicable Vendor will receive your contact information (including name, phone number and email address) and information regarding your Event (such as date, event type, location, venue and number of guests). We are not responsible for any consequences of any use or disclosure of your information by such Vendors and you assume all risk arising from such information sharing and your interaction with such Vendors.

_Information Shared with Our Services Providers_. We may engage third-party services providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf and are expressly obligated not to disclose or use your PII for any other purpose.

For example, we may share your PII and other information related to your payment methods with our third party payment processing services providers in order to process payment of any fees associated with the Vendor Matching feature, if applicable.

_Information Shared with Third Parties_. We may share anonymized or aggregated data we collect from the use of the Services, such as de-identified demographic information, de-identified location information, information about the computer or device from which you access the Services, market trends and other analysis that we create based on the information we receive from you and other Visitors, with third parties, including advertisers. Such information will never identify you or your employees, if any.

_Information Shared with Web Analytics Services Providers_.

**Google**. We utilize Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc., to gather information about how users engage with our Site and Services. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can opt out of Google’s collection and processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

**Facebook**. We may use certain tools offered by third parties (e.g., Facebook) to enable them to collect or receive information about actions users take on our Site and elsewhere on the internet through use of Cookies, Web Beacons and other storage technologies. These third parties may use the data that they collect to provide measurement services, targeted ads and other services. For more information regarding the collection and use of such information by Facebook, please see the Facebook [Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/), available at: <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

**Opt-out of Ad Tracking,** You can opt out of the collection and use of your information for ad targeting by going to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/> to limit collection through the Site or by configuring the settings on your mobile device to limit ad tracking through the App.

_Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions_. Information that we collect from our Visitors, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. Thus, if we are acquired by a third party as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale or if our assets are acquired by a third party in the event we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, some or all of our assets, including your PII, may be disclosed or transferred to a third party acquirer in connection with the transaction.

_Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others_. We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

### **Your Choices**

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your PII and we’ll respect the choices you make. Please note that if you decide not to provide us with the PII that we request, you may not be able to access all of the features of the Services.

_Communications_. We may periodically send you Advertising Material related to AllSeated and its partners based on or related to your use of the Services. When you receive Advertising Material from us, you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” (by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive). We do need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications – e.g., communications regarding Account management or updates to our Services, the TOU or this Privacy Policy.

_Modifying Your Information_. You can access and modify certain PII associated with your Account through the Services or by contacting us via email with your request at [allseated@allseated.com](mailto:allseated@allseated.com). Unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy, AllSeated will retain your information until you cancel your AllSeated Account, or until your AllSeated Account has been inactive for a year. If you want us to delete your PII and your Account, please contact us at [allseated@allseated.com](mailto:allseated@allseated.com) with your request. If you contact us we may, for your protection, ask you for additional information to verify your identity. In most cases, we will provide the access you request and correct or delete any inaccurate personal information you discover. We’ll take steps to delete your information as soon as we can, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. After deletion of your Account, you agree that we can continue to use your data in anonymized form.

Please note that the Services allow you to share information with other Account holders.  You understand and agree that if another Account holder has accessed any information that you have shared, including PII, we cannot change or limit what they do with that information outside of the Services.

**Responding to Do Not Track Signals**

Our Site does not have the capability to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from various web browsers.

**The Security of Your Information**

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure and to comply with all applicable laws. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

**International Transfer**

**Links to Other Sites**

Our Services may contain links to websites and services that are owned or operated by third parties (each, a “ **Third-Party Service** ”). Any information that you provide on or to a Third-Party Service or that is collected by a Third-Party Service is provided directly to the owner or operator of the Third-Party Service and is subject to the owner’s or operator’s privacy policy. We’re not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of any Third-Party Service. To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of all Third-party Services that you access.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California residents may request and obtain from us, once a year, free of charge, a list of third parties, if any, to which we disclosed their PII for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and the categories of PII shared with those third parties. If you are a California resident and wish to obtain that information, please submit your request by sending us an email at [allseated@allseated.com](mailto:allseated@allseated.com) with “California Privacy Information Request” in the subject line and in the body of your message. You may also submit a request by writing to us at 230 California St., Suite 420, San Francisco, CA 94111.

**Questions?**

Please contact us at [allseated@allseated.com](mailto:allseated@allseated.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.

Revised as of: February 2, 2016
